Guide to the International Brigades Archive, Moscow: Selected Images ALBA.PHOTO.177
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Folder 183: Portraits of 14th and 24th Battalion Volunteers, 1937
  - Tarr Jure [two soldiers in back of truck, children watching], 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183023)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/23
  - Tarr Jure [one man pictured], 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183024)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/24
  - Commissar of the 15th International Brigade, Bruni Weiger (?); Lieutenant Now with Dombrowski Battalion; Klein, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183025)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/25
  - [Troops posed in formation in a field], 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183026)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/26
  - Dimitrov Battalion at Jarama; Klein [in a trench], 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183027)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/27
  - Dimitrov Battalion at Jarama; Klein [man peers out of trench tunnel], 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183028)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/28
  - Dimitrov Battalion at Jarama; Klein [two men by a river], 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183029)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/29
  - Dimitrov Battalion at Jarama; Klein [five men], 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183030)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/30
  - Copic in the Center [group of soldiers], 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183031)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/31
  - Dimitrov Battalion at Jarama [group standing in a trench], 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183032)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/32
  - [Large group of men posed together, some with raised fists], 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183033)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/33
  - [Group of men pose in front of stone wall], 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183034)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/34
  - [Soldiers sit at table, two of them reading], 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183035)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/35
  - Left Republican Youth, Juventudes Socialistas Unificadas (J.S.U.), Juventudes Libertarias (J.L.), 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183038)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/38
  - Commander Aguila, 24th Batallion, 15 International Brigade near Azila, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9, Item 177_183039)
    Moscow Number: 5/183/39
- Folder 184: 15th International Brigade, 57th British Battalion, 1937-1938
  - Trenches at Fuentes de Ebro (Left, Fletcher; Center, Hamish Fraser; Right, Harry Dobson, PC), 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 10, Item 177_184003)
    Moscow Number: 5/184/3
  - Monument to Fallen Comrades, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 10, Item 177_184027)
    Moscow Number: 5/184/27
  - Clement Attlee Company (Veterans of Teruel), 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 10, Item 177_184030)
    Moscow Number: 5/184/30
- Folder 185: 58th Battalion (Lincoln) in Operations for the Republican Army in Spain, 1937-1938
  - Lincoln-Washington Battalion (Soldier with Light Machine Gun), 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 11, Item 177_185001)
    Moscow Number: 5/185/1
  - Lincoln-Washington Activities (Darmos) [three men, two using pick and shovel], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 11, Item 177_185005)
    Moscow Number: 5/185/5
  - Spanish Youth Organizers, J.S.U., J.L., American, Canadian, and Cuban Young Communist Leaguers visit Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 11, Item 177_185012)
    Moscow Number: 5/185/12
  - Lincoln-Washington Battalion (Morris Stamm and John Coon of Machine Gun Company at Gandesa Front) [using a machine gun], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 11, Item 177_185015)
    Moscow Number: 5/185/15
  - Hut built by Lincoln-Washington Comrades in Olive Grove near Azaila, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 11, Item 177_185027)
    Moscow Number: 5/185/27
  - Lincoln-Washington Comrades in Brigade "Shower Machine", 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 11, Item 177_185030)
    Moscow Number: 5/185/30
  - Lincoln-Washington Battalion (Matias Ferrado, Company 3, Gandesa Front), 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 11, Item 177_185032)
    Moscow Number: 5/185/32
  - Lincoln-Washington Battalion (Antonio Segovia, Company 3), 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 11, Item 177_185034)
    Moscow Number: 5/185/34
  - S. Salzman, MacKenzie-Papineau Observer, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 11, Item 177_185035)
    Moscow Number: 5/185/35
  - Lincoln-Washington Battalion (Yale Stuart), 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 11, Item 177_185036)
    Moscow Number: 5/185/36
  - Lincoln-Washington Battalion (Kitchen, Frying Hamburgers near Huesca), 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 11, Item 177_185042)
    Moscow Number: 5/185/42
  - Lincoln-Washington Battalion (Clement Markert, Observer at Gandesa Front), 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 11, Item 177_185044)
    Moscow Number: 5/185/44
  - Lincoln-Washington Battalion (Copic in trenches), 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 11, Item 177_185045)
    Moscow Number: 5/185/45
  - Jim Woulff (Wolf?) came via Grenada with the Lincoln Battalion, wounded by grenade at Belchite [missing part of jaw], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 11, Item 177_185049)
    Moscow Number: 5/185/49
  - Lincoln-Washington Battalion (Combat at Cedrilla "North Pole"), 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 11, Item 177_185052)
    Moscow Number: 5/185/52
  - Cuban and Spanish-Americans at Jarama, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 11, Item 177_185053)
    Moscow Number: 5/185/53
  - Lincoln-Washington Battalion [checking rifles], 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 11, Item 177_185054)
    Moscow Number: 5/185/54
- Folder 186: 59th Battalion at the Front during the Civil War, Jan 1938-Aug 1938
  - [Mother Bloor Machine Gun Section], Jan 1938-Aug 1938 (Box 1, Folder 12, Item 177_186009)
    Moscow Number: 5/186/9
  - [Built-up stone wall], Jan 1938-Aug 1938 (Box 1, Folder 12, Item 177_186012)
    Moscow Number: 5/186/12
  - [Soldier working with maps on a table], Jan 1938-Aug 1938 (Box 1, Folder 12, Item 177_186013)
    Moscow Number: 5/186/13
  - Men of 59th Battalion (Spanish) at Corbera, Jan 1938-Aug 1938 (Box 1, Folder 12, Item 177_186014)
    Moscow Number: 5/186/14
- Folder 187: 15th International Brigade, 60th Battalion (MacKenzie-Papineau) during Operations for Republican Army, Oct 1937 - Aug 1938
  - MacKenzie-Papineau Marching through Marca, Oct 1937-Aug 1938 (Box 1, Folder 13, Item 177_187001)
    Moscow Number: 5/187/1
  - MacKenzie-Papineau Marching at Marca, Oct 1937-Aug 1938 (Box 1, Folder 13, Item 177_187004)
    Moscow Number: 5/187/4
  - MacKenzie-Papineau Training, Oct 1937-Aug 1938 (Box 1, Folder 13, Item 177_187008)
    Moscow Number: 5/187/8
  - MacKenzie-Papineau at Marca, Oct 1937-Aug 1938 (Box 1, Folder 13, Item 177_187012)
    Moscow Number: 5/187/12
  - Presentation of Brigade Flag by JSU to MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Oct 1937-Aug 1938 (Box 1, Folder 13, Item 177_187019)
    Moscow Number: 5/187/19
  - MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Oct 1937-Aug 1938 (Box 1, Folder 13, Item 177_187027)
    Moscow Number: 5/187/27
  - MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Oct 1937-Aug 1938 (Box 1, Folder 13, Item 177_187030)
    Moscow Number: 5/187/30
  - MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion (Hut on Banks of Ebro River), Oct 1937-Aug 1938 (Box 1, Folder 13, Item 177_187048)
    Moscow Number: 5/187/48
  - MacKenzie-Papineau Fiesta, Oct 1937-Aug 1938 (Box 1, Folder 13, Item 177_187053)
    Moscow Number: 5/187/53
  - MacKenzie-Papineau (Frank Rogers, Commissar, Addressing Soldiers and Delegates of Popular Front, Ebro Front), Oct 1937-Aug 1938 (Box 1, Folder 13, Item 177_187061)
    Moscow Number: 5/187/61
  - MacKenzie-Papineau (Morris Brier and Otto Reeves), Oct 1937-Aug 1938 (Box 1, Folder 13, Item 177_187063)
    Moscow Number: 5/187/63
  - MacKenzie-Papineau (Machine Gun Instruction), Oct 1937-Aug 1938 (Box 1, Folder 13, Item 177_187064)
    Moscow Number: 5/187/64
- Folder 188: 15th International Brigade Volunteers, Portraits, 1937-1938
  - Theodore (Jarama), 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188001)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/1
  - Louie (Black Machine-Gunner), 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188002)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/2
  - Constantino Dubac, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188003)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/3
  - Tony Martini, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188004)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/4
  - Jim Brewer, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188005)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/5
  - John Power, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188006)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/6
  - Alf Christie, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188007)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/7
  - Chris Smith, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188008)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/8
  - Armedie Grenier, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188009)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/9
  - Michael Economides, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188010)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/10
  - Egon Jup, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188011)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/11
  - Raphael Moral Lopez, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188013)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/13
  - Langston Hughes Visits 15th International Brigade (Quinto), [standing smoking cigarette] [Duplicate of 177_188077], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188014)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/14
  - [Chivant, Political Commissar 2nd Battalion], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188015)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/15
  - Officer with cap and leather jacket, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188016)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/16
  - Lawrence Cohen, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188018)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/18
  - Adam Herter, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188019)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/19
  - Vaughn Love, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188020)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/20
  - Armentino Feria Perez, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188021)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/21
  - Raul Rojas, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188022)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/22
  - Gerald Shea, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188023)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/23
  - Owen Smith, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188024)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/24
  - Rico Rusciano, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188025)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/25
  - Martin Martinez Izquierdo, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188026)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/26
  - George Fletcher, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188027)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/27
  - Arthur Nicoll, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188028)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/28
  - Miguel Vazquez, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188030)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/30
  - Robert Reed, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188031)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/31
  - Deszo Beke, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188032)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/32
  - Seguro de los Banos (After Fascist Air Raid), 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188033)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/33
  - Emanuel Arkas (Chief Mechanic, 15th International Brigade Auto Park), 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188034)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/34
  - [Officer in cap, jacket posed against wall], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188035)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/35
  - Costas Lapithiotis (Central Committee, Communist Party of Cyprus; Came to Spain from London), 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188036)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/36
  - Bobby Walker, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188037)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/37
  - Jim Ruskin, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188038)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/38
  - Reginald David, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188039)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/39
  - Francisco Tarancon, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188040)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/40
  - Spartaco, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188041)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/41
  - Frank Roden, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188042)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/42
  - Frazer Thomas (?), 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188043)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/43
  - Gilberto Acosta Alba, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188044)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/44
  - Donald Thayer, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188045)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/45
  - Jack Hoshooley, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188046)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/46
  - William Griffiths, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188047)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/47
  - Frank Rogers, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188048)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/48
  - George Watt, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188049)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/49
  - Mick Myers, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188050)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/50
  - Morris Davis, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188051)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/51
  - Ernest Osbourne, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188052)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/52
  - Easey Goldstein, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188053)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/53
  - Alan Gilchrist, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188054)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/54
  - Dinah, Henri Barbusse Company, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188057)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/57
  - Harry Dobson, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188058)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/58
  - Joe Taylor, 15th International Brigade Scout, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188059)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/59
  - ? at Quinto, Belchite, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188060)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/60
  - Captain Roslim Commandant 2nd Battalion, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188061)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/61
  - Joe Dallet (Killed in Action, Fuentes de Ebro), 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188062)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/62
  - Major Crespo (Near Huesca), 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188063)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/63
  - Albert Maas, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188064)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/64
  - [Black soldier portrait], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188065)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/65
  - Young, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188066)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/66
  - John Gollan, (with interpreter speaks to British Battalion, Tarrega), 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188067)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/67
  - [Three soldiers talking in front of a car], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188068)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/68
  - David Guest [Duplicate of 177_188079], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188069)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/69
  - Gomes Luis Pedro Boni, 15th International Brigade, Almendro, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188070)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/70
  - [Soldier wearing coat, hill visible in background] [Duplicate of 177_188078], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188071)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/71
  - [Three officers walking from a building], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188072)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/72
  - [Soldier portrait, wearing jacket, no hat], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188073)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/73
  - [Soldier portrait posed in front of a stone wall], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188074)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/74
  - [Man posed with black dog, handwriting at top of image (difficult to read, but probably explains who this is)], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188075)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/75
  - [Man posed with black dog, no handwriting at top of image], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188076)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/76
  - Langston Hughes Visits 15th International Brigade (Quinto), [standing smoking cigarette] [Dup of 177_188014], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188077)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/77
  - [Soldier wearing coat, hill visible in background] [Duplicate of 177_188071], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188078)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/78
  - [David Guest] [Duplicate of 177_188069], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188079)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/79
  - [Jack Mulliger, Chief of Scouts] [Duplicate of 177-188090], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188080)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/80
  - Al Tanz, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188081)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/81
  - Martino Martin, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188082)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/82
  - [Black and Spanish soldiers posed together], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188083)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/83
  - [Two men seated at table by open window, one smoking], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188084)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/84
  - [Soldier with rifle and blanket/poncho draped over his shoulders], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188085)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/85
  - Zanella Marino, 1st Company, 2nd Battalion, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188087)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/87
  - Jack Mulliger, Chief of Scouts [Duplicate of 177-188080], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188090)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/90
  - [Soldier poses on motorcycle, driving goggles on forehead], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188091)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/91
  - [Bill Rogers, name in caption at bottom of photo], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188092)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/92
  - Lieutenant Pedro Sanchez, Head of 15th International Brigade Auto Park, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188093)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/93
  - Johnson, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188094)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/94
  - Digges, Adjutant to Merriman, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188095)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/95
  - Easey Goldstein (Headquarters of "Rolling Park," 15th International Brigade Auto Park), 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188096)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/96
  - Kelly, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188098)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/98
  - Nicoletto, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188099)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/99
  - [Officer with hat and round glasses, writing on photo hard to read but probably reveals who this is], 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14, Item 177_188100)
    Moscow Number: 5/188/100
- Folder 189: 15th International Brigade, Group Photographs with Identifications, 1937
  - Commander Steve Nelson (Group), 1937 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 177_189006)
    Moscow Number: 5/189/6
  - [Three soldiers in white shirts, dark pants pose together], 1937 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 177_189008)
    Moscow Number: 5/189/8
  - Members of Independent Labour Party Contingent at the Huesca Front (Partido Obrero de Unificación Marxista [POUM] Division). 1) Jack Ritchie; 2) Jones; 3) Middlestone; 4) Dr. Louis Levin; 5) Parker; 6) Frankford; 7) Gottman; 8) Arthuro [also includes Charles Doran, Patrick O'Hara, Philip Hunter and John Braithwaite], 1937 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 177_189009)
    Moscow Number: 5/189/9
  - John Gollan with John Gates at British Battalion, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 177_189010)
    Moscow Number: 5/189/10
  - Lt. Francis and Charlotte Haldane, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 177_189011)
    Moscow Number: 5/189/11
  - John Gates, Cohen, Minor, and Reid, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 177_189015)
    Moscow Number: 5/189/15
  - 1) John Braithwaite; 2) Harry Milton; 3) Philip Hunter; 4) Eric Blair [George Orwell]; 5) Eileen Blair; 6) Middlestone at La Granja, Huesca, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 177_189016)
    Moscow Number: 5/189/16
  - Minor, Browder, North and Reid, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 177_189020)
    Moscow Number: 5/189/20
  - 15 International Brigade, Battalion Commanders near Azila 1) Bob Thompson, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion; 2) Phil Detro, Acting Commander; 3) Garcia, 24th Battalion; 4) O'Dair, British Battalion; 5) Aguila, 24th Battalion, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 177_189030)
    Moscow Number: 5/189/30
  - Left, Saul Wellman; Center, Bob Thompson; Right, Dave Doran at Fuentes de Ebro, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 177_189033)
    Moscow Number: 5/189/33
  - [Four soldiers standing in a trench], 1937 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 177_189034)
    Moscow Number: 5/189/34
  - 15th International Brigade, Sanidad Leaders; Dr. Bernstein; Dr. Strauss (Head); Al Goldberg (Commissar), 1937 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 177_189035)
    Moscow Number: 5/189/35
  - Lieutenant Kelly and Battalion Staff (Tarazona), 1937 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 177_189036)
    Moscow Number: 5/189/36
  - Lederer and Tschapiev, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 177_189038)
    Moscow Number: 5/189/38
  - Klaus and Barthel with Prisoner, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 177_189039)
    Moscow Number: 5/189/39
  - Russian (?), 1937 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 177_189040)
    Moscow Number: 5/189/40
  - Bob Cooney, Antonio Gil Cabezas, Frank Rogers, Jose M. Varella, George Watt, Sandor Voros, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 177_189041)
    Moscow Number: 5/189/41
  - [Five men (four faces visible) pose at railyard with some supplies], 1937 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 177_189042)
    Moscow Number: 5/189/42
  - [Two-man indoor portrait pose, one seated], 1937 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 177_189043)
    Moscow Number: 5/189/43
  - Dan Kramen, Tom Swann, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 177_189044)
    Moscow Number: 5/189/44
  - "Francisco," Keller, Wolff, and Galleani, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 177_189045)
    Moscow Number: 5/189/45
  - [English antifascist group], 1937 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 177_189047)
  - Herbert Weiman (?), 1937 (Box 2, Folder 15, Item 177_189046)
    Moscow Number: 5/189/46
- Folder 190: 15th International Brigade Volunteers, Unidentified
  - [Closeup portrait of clean-shaven soldier, slightly out of focus], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190001)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/1
  - [Man posed in front of a small tree], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190002)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/2
  - [Men cleaning up rubble on a city street], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190003)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/3
  - [Officers, colorguard, soldiers march through town], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190004)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/4
  - [Man (face mostly washed out) sitting in wingback chair], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190005)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/5
  - [Soldier poses on side of road], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190006)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/6
  - [Man and woman portrait smiling together], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190007)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/7
  - [Man cooking with skillet over an open fire under a tree], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190008)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/8
  - [Man with hat, glasses, moustache poses near exterior building wall], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190009)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/9
  - [Wide shot soldier in open doorway], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190010)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/10
  - [Soldier poses near building surrounded by trees], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190011)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/11
  - [Soldier with open book, big black boots poses seated on stone wall], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190012)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/12
  - [Man shirtless by river (?)], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190013)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/13
  - [Man in dark shirt closeup in shade under trees], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190014)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/14
  - [Officer with hat and glasses against wall, blurry], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190015)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/15
  - [Man in oxford shirt poses near trench, sandbags], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190016)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/16
  - [Soldier in peacoat, beret, head bandage (?)], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190017)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/17
  - [Soldier with leather bag strap across chest, trees in background], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190018)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/18
  - [Soldier in posed against wall], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190019)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/19
  - [Soldier with open shirt], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190020)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/20
  - [Soldier portrait outdoors], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190021)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/21
  - [Soldier portrait outdoors], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190022)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/22
  - [Soldier with open shirt portrait outdoors], undated (Box 2, Folder 16, Item 177_190023)
    Moscow Number: 5/190/23